Narrator: 1
was / were and could
Speaker 1: Gordon was Jeremy’s business partner.
They were at his country house.
They could hear a strange noise.
Speaker 2: She wasn’t at home last night.
You weren’t very nice to her.
I couldn’t sleep.
Speaker 3: Were you ill yesterday? When was he born?
Could you see anybody in the library?
Narrator: 2
regular verbs
Speaker 2: I really liked the present. She wanted to be a doctor.
Speaker 3: She didn’t enjoy the concert. They didn’t arrive until very late.
Speaker 2: Did you watch the match last night? When did you finish the book?
Narrator: 3
irregular verbs
Speaker 3: I went to Paris last summer. She slept on the sofa.
Speaker 2: He didn’t come home last night. They didn’t hear the music.
Speaker 1: Did you speak to your sister yesterday? Where did you have lunch?